sub by kisskh.me
Sometimes, the reality you're facing
seems unrealistic.
Like right now,
as I'm walking the streets
covered in white
after an unexpected snow.
METAPHORS OF DAWN
YU HYEON-U EXHIBITION
It's the same when you're in love.
It feels like you've become
the most special person in the world.
It feels unrealistic.
Your heart…
flutters.
It's so erotic.
I know.
THE MOST BEAUTIFUL MOMENT OF A LOVER
VIEW FROM BEHIND
NABI
YU HYEON-U
But why is it called "Nabi"?
I don't know.
Let's go.
-What should we see next?
-Let's check this out.
This one?
-Have you heard of him?
-Of course.
Na-bi.
Isn't it pretty?
Yu Na-bi!
What is love?
He was a serious person.
Constantly giving meaning…
to something abstract and unfamiliar.
Wouldn't that be true love?
-I knew it.
-What?
I asked to have pizza today
because I wanted to get a glimpse
of your feelings
through the act of sharing food.
-My feelings?
-Yes.
Your feelings for me.
Whether or not this one layer comes
between us tonight
will confirm
the sincerity of our relationship.
Almost always…
No.
He was always…
Honestly, this is ridiculous.
What do you mean?
I wish you wouldn't make
such arbitrary decisions.
Do my nails look that strange?
Everyone said they were pretty.
"Everyone"? If I were you,
I would've asked for my opinion first.
I guess I'm nothing
but a mere stranger to you.
Am I the only one who's serious?
He obsessively put meaning into everything
and made endless metaphors.
Was my work embarrassing to you?
Is that why you're crying?
Na-bi. Don't just look at the exterior.
You have to look at the meaning
hidden inside it.
You could've asked me about it first.
Darn it!
You're making me really upset.
I thought you would understand me
the best.
I once believed that it was special.
I'm not sure if I'd like that!
It's a bit strange.
He said it's because he loves you.
Artists don't use just any model,
you know.
I think
he must really care about you.
You're like his muse.
-No, this is really weird.
-His muse?
This is art.
You call this art?
It looks fine.
I was confused…
about boundaries.
Excuse me.
Your boyfriend's name
is Yu Hyeon-u, right?
Yes. Why?
I'm not sure if I should tell you, but…
My friend attends that academy.
It's already been a while.
I realized the truth…
at an unexpected moment.
And to be honest,
I felt like I already knew it.
But…
Na-bi.
I'm swamped with the academy
and the exhibition.
If the exhibition's successful,
I'll quit being a teacher
and focus on my art career.
But I'm not sure what theme I should do.
Mr. Baek wants to express people
in their 20s as lively and free…
But this jerk talked too much
for me to just blame myself.
Na-bi.
Why are you sitting like that?
I'm talking about something serious.
You asshole.
What?
Love.
It gets trampled on
and helplessly melts away.
It's nothing.
My relationship ended like that too.
-Na-bi, where are you going?
-The studio.
Okay, see you later.
See you.
-What are you doing?
-Just chilling.
Hurry back.
Aren't you going to the studio?
-Go ahead first.
-Hi.
-Hey.
Hi.
Hi, Na-bi.
Where were you, Na-bi?
Just outside.
Na-bi, help me.
You should do it yourself.
Na-bi, can't you concentrate
for a few hours?
Jeez, what a jerk.
What is it this time?
He's the one who suggested
going to a hotel instead of a motel.
And now he wants me to chip in.
Who? The guy you met
through the app yesterday?
Yes!
I wouldn't feel this upset if he was good.
It wasn't even worth spending
a night with him!
-Why'd you sleep with him, then?
-He must've been handsome.
She loves handsome guys.
This is so annoying. Let's go for a smoke.
No, I'm quitting for a while.
I'm not going to smoke for three days.
What's in three days?
A blind date.
I'll quit until then,
and if it's bearable, I'll keep it up.
-Another blind date?
-You're unbelievable.
Do you like men that much?
You're one to ask.
Point taken.
It's too noisy here.
-You're going to work, right?
-Yes.
-You're really not going?
-Bye.
Then who can I smoke with?
What if I get kidnapped
while smoking alone?
-I wonder if my mother would cry for--
-I'll come with you.
You're the best.
I just got here.
-All right, I'm coming.
-Just a little more.
Do you climb up all these stairs
every time you smoke?
-I don't mind if it's for a drag.
-Gosh.
If he's okay, swipe right.
If not, swipe left.
And if you both swipe right
for each other, it's a match.
And then?
Then you message back and forth here.
If it goes well, you exchange numbers
and maybe meet up later.
I guess today is not the day.
But nobody uses
their real names here, right?
Right. I don't show my face
on my profile, either.
But some people just reveal
their names and faces.
Oh, I hate tattoos like this!
Tattoos?
The guy I met yesterday
had a huge tattoo, too.
You know what it said?
His thing kept dying,
and he says "never die"?
-How--
-Keep it down.
It was so ridiculous.
Some tattoos are pretty, though.
Like whose?
What?
Are you seeing someone?
What are you on about?
As if I would.
Do you want to join us for drinks later?
No, I'm fine.
I'm going to work late today.
Again?
-Life must be so boring for you.
-Whatever.
Look. He's one of our juniors.
He said he wants to drink with you.
When will I finish?
I stayed up all night.
I'm going to have to stay up again.
I just got out of a relationship,
remember?
Hey, I didn't mean that.
We all know each other except for you.
So I just wanted to introduce you two.
Well, anyway…
God, you're so boring.
Oh, no! I accidentally swiped left
-on a total hottie!
-Let me see.
I can never see him again.
You're acting unlike yourself today.
What? What is it this time?
Oh, well. You got rid of that jerk,
so you should move on.
-But this app isn't for you.
-Why not?
You're pretty
but you have no taste in men.
-You'll only attract losers.
-Hey!
What?
Well…
Maybe.
-You're really not coming?
-No.
Have fun.
You're so boring.
Call me later!
Okay.
EPISODE 1: THERE'S NO SUCH THING AS FATE.
NEVERTHELESS,
THE DAY SHE BROKE UP WITH X
You got here first.
Who are you?
Aren't you So-ri?
No, my name is Yu Na-bi.
Na-bi?
I guess I mistook you for someone else.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
It's silly, but the moment our eyes met…
The pain of the breakup
that had been weighing down on me
just a minute ago…
Can I sit here?
You're already sitting there.
Are you with someone?
No, I'm not.
…melted away like snow.
But aren't you here to meet someone?
You said you mistook me for someone else.
I canceled on her.
Why?
I just thought…
I didn't need to meet her.
The loser grants the winner a wish.
Remember?
I've been conned.
Keep going.
So you broke up today?
Oh.
Yes.
I flat out dumped him.
I guess he was a bad guy.
Well…
he was a total joke.
I was an idiot for dating him.
Good riddance. Now nothing holds me back
from leaving the country.
-For travel?
-Exchange student.
I want to go to Paris.
That's cool.
But it won't happen anytime soon.
Do you like traveling?
I've never traveled properly before.
-I want to go at the end of the year.
-With who?
Alone?
With a friend? Or…
your girlfriend?
I'm not sure.
With anyone.
Here you go.
It's my turn now, right?
Why is it so hard?
Because you haven't done it often.
If you keep practicing,
you'll get the hang of it.
It doesn't matter where it hits.
Just try to get it near the red dot.
Easy.
That's unexpected.
What do you mean?
You look a bit different when you smile.
What are you talking about?
Move over.
I won.
Of course you did.
You seem happy for a loser.
Well…
it was fun.
Right.
It's fun to be with you, Na-bi.
This guy…
is bad for my heart.
Okay.
Easy.
YU JEONG-RAN
Yes, Mom.
Na-bi.
Your aunt made your favorite side dish.
-Should I ask her to send it to you?
-No…
I still have a lot left over
from last time.
Just throw away the leftovers
and eat the new ones she sends.
You always tell me to throw away stuff.
I'm hanging up now.
Why are you in such a mood?
I want my precious daughter
to have new and good stuff.
Anyway, it's fine.
When are you coming home?
It's only an hour away by subway
but you never come home.
Because he's there…
I just have a lot of assignments
these days.
How is Ttoli?
Ttoli is always whimpering
because she misses you.
Bring your boyfriend.
I'll treat you to delicious food.
There's no boyfriend.
What? Did you break up?
Na-bi.
Mom, I need to hang up.
What?
Why were you named after a butterfly?
So my life could be sweet like honey.
My mom and aunt named me.
I'm just kidding.
Do you know Nathaniel Hawthorne?
He's my aunt's favorite author,
and he said this.
It's a bit cringey to quote it.
"Happiness is like a butterfly which,
when pursued, is always beyond our grasp,
but, if you will sit down quietly,
may alight upon you."
That's the back story.
It's nothing special.
No…
I love it.
Is that a butterfly…
on your neck?
Yes.
I like…
butterflies.
All done.
It's cute.
Is this really your wish?
That was pretty simple.
Then should I…
make another wish?
This is silly.
What do you mean?
It's nothing.
The moon is pretty today.
Do you want one?
It's my last one.
Well…
I don't smoke.
Excuse me.
Can I borrow a cigarette?
Gosh.
I'm sobering up.
Hey, can I borrow a cigarette?
If we run into each other next time,
I promise to return the favor.
I do have one, but…
What the hell?
What?
Why are you smiling?
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm fine.
Do you want to go see butterflies?
Where would we see them?
At my place.
Let me go to the bathroom for a minute.
What are you doing?
I miss you too.
Are you going to sleep?
Yes.
What? So you just left?
Did you contact him after that?
Of course not.
I told him about where my name came from,
but I don't even know his name.
You mustered up your courage, though.
Too bad.
What's that?
Oh, this?
Well…
It's nothing.
It's love.
It's nothing like that.
-Then what is it?
-Lust?
I don't know. It's just…
It was fun.
It's hard to find someone
you feel an instant connection with.
Never mind that.
You said he has a girlfriend.
You should never hang out with cheaters.
Oh, right.
I have to post the part-time job ad.
Or should I ask some of the kids?
All right.
How about Jae-eon?
I'm not sure. Would he do it?
I'll try to convince him.
Hello.
Oh, do, re, mi, fa, sol. Sol is here.
I have a meeting with the professor.
Right. Go inside with Na-bi.
-Together?
It's okay. Sol can have the meeting first.
It'll be a waste of time.
It's about
the exchange student program, right?
The professor's nagging will get longer
if it's one-on-one.
Right.
Bye, then.
Bye.
You're really clueless, aren't you?
What do you mean?
Na-bi was feeling uncomfortable since
she didn't want to be compared to Sol.
Is that so?
You only picked hard places to get in.
Na-bi, it'll be difficult to get
accepted to any of these schools.
You know that, right?
Yes.
I'm not saying you're bad.
You're doing well,
but there are only
a limited number of spots.
You have to raise your GPA.
Work harder, okay?
Yes, ma'am.
And going abroad isn't always
the best answer.
Staying in Korea could be a better option.
Domestic graduate schools
are pretty good too.
There's no place like Korea for Koreans,
don't you think?
Right.
Let's talk again next time, then.
What about you, Sol?
You didn't submit your list?
No, not yet.
You could start next semester.
What are you waiting for?
Is there something going on?
No.
I'll make my decision soon, ma'am.
All right.
I'd prefer it if you made it quick.
It's a waste of time.
You might think it won't be any different.
But there are things you can learn
from the world out there.
This is a great list.
Take a look at this,
and make your decision.
LIST OF PROSPECTIVE UNIVERSITIES
Yes, ma'am.
Why do you two look so gloomy?
You should be shining at that age.
Don't stay holed up in the studio.
You should make your life eventful
to get inspiration for your work.
Got that?
Yes.
I think she said the word "inspiration"
over 100 times.
Just take it.
I was about to give you the file
if you needed it anyway.
Thanks. It'll be helpful.
It was so embarrassing, though.
What was?
I listed up all the great universities
without thinking about my grades.
I'm jealous, Sol.
You can go pretty much anywhere.
It might not be the best idea
to go abroad.
Honestly, it kind of feels like
I'm just trying to run away.
Were you thinking that too?
Yun Sol!
Oh, you were with Na-bi.
What did the professor say?
Why did she call you two?
It was for the exchange--
Just talking about assignment ideas.
Assignment ideas?
Why did she leave me out?
This is favoritism.
She just gave us a bit of advice.
We'll be off.
Oh, okay. Bye.
Bye, Na-bi.
I'm the one who's out of ideas.
Why are you dressed so nicely?
Do I look nice? That's a relief.
Is it because we're gathering today?
Well…
my blind date was supposed to be tomorrow,
but he said something urgent came up
and asked if we could meet today.
Otherwise, it'll be a while later.
You know how you shouldn't
put off a blind date for too long.
So I just agreed to meet him today.
What? Then what about our gathering today?
Tell the others for me.
Hey, I didn't want to go.
You're the one who made a fuss.
I know. I'm really sorry.
But if you don't go either,
everyone will curse me to death. Please?
-Sol, please.
-Gosh.
All right.
I love you!
If things go well with my date,
I'll set you up with someone too.
There's no need.
Oh, come on.
-Hi. What brings you here?
-Hello.
-Keep working.
-Okay.
I already chiseled it off.
You have to raise your GPA.
So you're really going to stay up working?
Yes.
Or I might not be able to finish on time.
My progress is slow.
Alcohol is the best when you're stuck.
I'm going to go drink with the kids.
You don't know any of our juniors.
Don't you need an assistant
for the exhibit?
At this rate, you'll be the first one
in our department to do everything alone.
Gosh. Never mind.
There's no way
you'll get a new boyfriend like that.
Bye.
Call me if you change your mind.
Okay.
Have fun!
I will!
That will be 14,000 won.
Here.
It's him.
Hang on.
The library, and now this.
I must be losing my mind.
You're really not coming?
Bit-na, where's the location?
We meet again.
What are you doing here?
Hey, you're here.
-Hi. I'm heading in first.
-Okay.
He's the junior…
who was hoping to drink with you.
I see.
Look! You're screwed.
Gosh, this place is flooded with seniors.
Seniors!
Are you sick of your seniors?
Not at all!
But we have a newbie now.
She made a rare appearance,
so be nice to her.
This is Yu Na-bi,
and this is Park Jae-eon.
Park Jae-eon…
Oh, okay.
His name was Park Jae-eon.
What's with the face?
Do you know each other?
No.
-It's our first time seeing each other.
-It's your first time?
They took turns taking a leave.
And Na-bi barely attends school events.
-That's right. She never shows up.
-But you come to all of them.
Hi.
Oh. Hi.
I just got butterflies in my stomach!
"Oh. Hi."
I'm getting butterflies!
I'm Park Jae-eon.
I'll just talk to you casually.
He's the same age as us.
He was a business major at K University
but he took the entrance exam again
to major in sculpture.
I see.
I saw you before, though.
What?
Where?
At school.
I said I wanted to drink with you.
Right.
So you two have finally met.
It's nice to meet you.
It's nice to meet you too.
I don't believe…
in fate or love anymore.
But this situation…
It's pretty unrealistic.
That professor gives us
so many assignments. It's awful.
You selected a bad course.
You took that class.
Why didn't you tell me?
-Ji-wan's still not answering?
-No.
She's not reading my messages.
I guess she's still with him.
She said she'd make it quick.
Things must be going well.
Hey, that's a given.
Ji-wan's popular with guys.
I'm so jealous.
So many guys asked for her number
at our high school festival.
But it seems like Ji-wan
likes the guy this time, too.
There's no point.
Bet she'll get sick of him within a month.
Right.
It's her biggest wish to go on a
couple's trip for a one-year anniversary.
-That's so cute.
-It's cute.
-I'll get it.
-It'll be hard to carry it all yourself.
No, it's fine.
Keep talking.
Right, so what happened?
He has a girlfriend.
Oh, my gosh.
I'm so sorry.
I'm okay.
Are you all right?
Yes.
I was looking at my phone.
I'm okay.
-Exciting! So much fun! The Game of Death!
Three! One!
-Two!
-Three!
Take off your hat.
-Hey. Here's a hair tie.
-Take it off.
Make a palm tree.
Go easy on me, please.
Jae-eon is fun.
You look pretty.
Jae-eon!
I'm sorry.
Off you go.
That look really suits you!
I'm really sorry, but…
Oh, you want a glass?
No…
If it's okay with you…
Could you watch me dance?
Don't cover your face!
-Five, six, seven, eight!
-Jae-eon has a way of
making naughty pranks seem rather fun.
Twist your body!
What is that?
Come on!
This is so stupid.
Are you upset?
I guess he smiles a lot.
-Let's play another game.
-What?
-Let's drink.
-It's nothing.
-Come on. Drink up.
It's mine.
Come on. Cheers!
-Cheers!
Can you hand me that?
Thanks.
-Hey, guys. Gather round.
-What is it?
Who are the scumbags who did it
in the student council room last semester?
Then is it true that a condom was found
in the trash can?
That's disgusting!
The sofa…
On the sofa?
You better fess up. Could it have been…
Quit playing detective.
You're barking up the wrong tree.
What?
Do you know who it is?
-Who is it?
-Get off me.
Goodness.
Do you still not know?
It's Choi Min-u.
No way!
-His girlfriend is Jeong-a.
-Then it was her and Min-u?
Of course not. He was sleeping
with someone else.
He was cheating on her?
That asshole!
How could he do that to her?
I feel sorry for her.
There are quite some pretty girls
who have poor judgment.
No wonder you're called Bit-na News.
Go, Bit-na News!
Stop overreacting.
Let me pour you a shot.
-Oh, thank you.
-This is boring, isn't it?
-Is your source reliable?
-Should we leave?
-Don't be ridiculous.
-Stay out of it.
-More drinks!
-Whose glass is empty?
-Me!
-You should take a break.
-Here you go.
-Thank you, my dear.
-You're the best.
-So how did you find out?
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
You dropped this.
Oh. Thank you.
Look at him.
You look a bit different when you smile.
I'm going to the bathroom for a bit.
Okay.
Why do I feel so annoyed?
I should just get back to work.
I'm going to go buy ice cream.
Do you want to come with me?
What do you want?
That one?
No.
Then…
what about that one?
No.
This one.
Why did you laugh?
Because you're cute.
Shut up.
Your style looks different.
Hey, what are you doing?
Let's skip study hall and go play games.
Sorry!
Why did you say you didn't know me?
Well…
I was caught off-guard.
It would've been strange to say
that I knew you.
I didn't know your name or your age.
So why did you just leave that day?
I was drunk.
Anyway, the stuff I said that day…
Just forget everything.
What about that day?
You didn't say much.
Well…
Just forget about it.
Don't worry. I won't say anything.
Okay.
You didn't erase it.
Oh, this?
Right.
I washed it, but it wouldn't come off.
That's strange.
It was a water-based marker.
Oh, really?
That's strange.
Didn't you want to see me again?
Well…
Not much.
But I was pretty startled.
I thought I'd never see you again.
I was glad…
to see you again.
Why are you two coming in together?
We bought ice cream.
Love always begins with ice cream,
you know.
Come here!
Hey! Let's go for a smoke.
Okay.
Do you want to come?
She doesn't smoke.
Really?
Be careful on the way out.
Darn it…
Here. This is my number.
If you text me your bank account number
and the cost, I'll send the money.
All right. I'll keep in touch.
I'm really sorry.
It's fine.
Your head's a bit red. Are you okay?
It's okay. My head is rock-hard.
Are you not hurt?
I ran into you pretty hard.
I'm okay.
That's a relief, then.
Let's go.
Why don't we just go
for another round somewhere?
Hello? Everyone here?
Hey, let's go.
Let's do that. All right.
-I'm off.
-Let's go together.
-Let's go.
-We're leaving.
-Goodbye!
-Good night!
Be careful on the way home.
You seemed to have drunk a lot.
Are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine. I'm not even drunk.
What about you?
Is that your girlfriend?
What?
I don't have a girlfriend.
I'm taking the bus here.
Careful on the way home.
Right. Bye.
We meet again.
I like…
butterflies.
I was glad…
to see you again.
I don't have a girlfriend.
Is this fate?
OH BIT-NA
Guys, send 20,000 won each for the drinks.
PARK JAE-EON
Why are you awake?
Right now?
Is it okay for me to come over?
I SENT THE MONEY
I SENT THE MONEY TOO
Is he sleeping?
He's sleeping already?
What am I doing?
Are you sleeping?
Darn it. Not you.
SCULPTURE STUDIO 3
Hey, Sol.
Aren't you going for a smoke?
I already did.
I see.
Hey, guys.
Aren't you going out for a smoke?
Just go. I'm totally busy right now.
Go away.
What about you?
No. This isn't sticking.
-You're really not going?
-Just go.
Hi.
Hi, Na-bi.
Hey, Na-bi.
Oh, hi.
What is it, Na-bi?
What?
It's nothing.
-I thought it was due today.
-I have to work late.
-Na-bi.
-Hey.
-Are you looking for someone?
-No.
I'm just getting some fresh air.
Professor!
-Professor!
Hey, a five-year-old
would do a better job.
Professor!
Professor, can you help me?
Gyeong-jun! Please!
No matter how many colors I mix,
I can't get the right color.
I won't help you
unless you call me Mr. An.
But you're our senior.
I will be so grateful
if you could help me with this.
-No.
-Mr. An!
See? He calls me Mr. An.
-Gyeong-jun! Mr. An!
-I need your help.
-What should I do?
-Just apply the second layer
and coat it with primer in the end. Okay?
PARK JAE-EON
He's in the group chat room, though.
Mr. An!
What are you doing?
-Gyeong-jun! I mean, Mr. An!
-Hello, ma'am.
-Why were you startled?
-Mr. An, please.
I'm more startled at your piece.
Why is there no progress?
-I can't seem to get the color right.
-Well, I…
I'm almost done.
This shouldn't be "almost done." Okay?
I'll work late today.
Working late isn't going to…
-Let's talk later.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Hey, Bit-na.
-What?
Did everyone send the money last night?
What? Yes, everyone sent it.
Why?
I was just curious.
They all sent it.
Jae-eon gave it to me in cash right away.
Oh.
Keep going.
Focus, all right?
I am.
I'm so full.
My stomach's going to explode.
Mine first.
I can't breathe.
But I can still eat dessert.
I can totally eat cake.
I can eat cake too!
I can eat it with coffee!
We have some time left. Shall we?
-Sure, you little foodie.
-You guys are coming too, right?
Of course.
Your stomachs are really going to explode.
He always picks a fight
when he's going to join us anyway.
Tell me about it.
Oh, no.
Where are my Bluetooth earphones?
I left them at the outdoor studio.
Someone's going to steal them for sure.
There are security cameras everywhere.
Nobody will take them.
Right?
It's so far away.
-I'll just ask in our chat room.
-Wait. I'll get them.
Really?
Yes.
It's fine. You don't need to.
No, I was about to go back anyway.
I'll get them and put them in your locker.
Send me your passcode.
I'm so touched.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
She's so kind.
What should I do?
I'm so popular.
Dream on. She'd never fall for you.
I was just saying!
Why would she do that for me?
She was going to head back anyway.
Never mind. Let's go have some cake.
Yes!
What's this? Is it a bat?
A bat? It's a butterfly.
This piece sure feels different
from all the other ones.
Right.
I don't even see him often at the studio.
When did he do all this?
He must be a genius.
Jae-eon won almost
all the competitions last year.
And he's even handsome.
Life's so unfair, isn't it?
So that was Jae-eon's.
But where did Jae-eon…
Oh. Hi, Na-bi.
Hi.
What brings you here?
Well…
Jin-su said he left something behind.
Did you see Bluetooth earphones
lying around?
-No.
You should look around.
Okay, I will.
Oh, Jae-eon!
Hey, Jae-eon.
Hey.
Hi, Jae-eon.
Hi.
Looking for something?
No.
Jae-eon, that's a butterfly, right?
She said it looks like a bat.
You recognized it?
Everyone thinks it's a bat.
You must really like butterflies.
-Your last piece was one too.
-Do you want to see my butterflies?
Yes. Show us.
Yes, please.
They're so pretty.
Is that what your tattoo is about?
Like people get tattoos of their pets?
Do they have names?
No, I just call them butterflies.
"Butterfly."
It's a pretty name.
I like…
butterflies.
"Butterfly."
It's a pretty name.
Jae-eon keeps making me think
the way my annoying ex did.
It's so stupid to read too much into
meaningless stuff.
You idiot.
Who's an idiot?
Don't look.
Is this seaweed?
Why did you have to appear out of nowhere
and surprise me like that?
You're just insensitive.
You left without a word.
I thought you had something to say.
No, I didn't have anything…
I was just looking
for my friend's belongings.
You know how popular you are, right?
That's why you have that look
and talk that way.
What?
There's the seaweed.
-Come here.
-Sorry.
I'm sorry! Stop it.
-Wipe it off.
-Okay, I will.
I'll wipe it off for you.
-Sorry! Okay, I'll really wipe it off.
-Hang on.
-You'd better.
-What?
-Come on, wipe it off.
-When did they get so close?
They look pretty good together. Hey!
What?
Let's just go.
-Why?
-Come on. Let's go.
Why do my shoulders hurt so much?
I wish they had high bars at school.
Relax.
Your back was hunched
when you were working.
Hey, let go. Wait.
Wait. Stop.
I almost fell down.
Bit-na says
you practically live in the studio.
Not really.
I like working at night,
so I often stay late. What about you?
I might try it more often.
It was fun.
As we talk,
I can see different sides of Jae-eon.
I envy you.
It used to be fun for me a long time ago.
It's not fun anymore?
There's a lot to think about now.
And I'm not sure what to do.
You wanted to be an exchange student.
It seems like a good goal.
It's nothing.
It sounds special,
but lots of students do it.
And honestly…
I just want to go somewhere far away.
Why?
Because of my mom and…
Let's stop talking about this.
It's boring.
It's not boring to me.
You're talking about your true self.
He's different from
the first impression I had of him.
I wanted to believe
that only I knew this side of him.
There's the moon you like.
It's pretty.
Your number.
Oh. My number?
It feels like something new
is about to begin.
I'm probably not mistaken.
Yu Na-bi. I saved your number.
You know that I'm Na-bi.
Do you want one?
No, thanks.
Did you get it customized?
Yes.
Isn't it pretty?
Another butterfly.
Oh, show me too.
-What?
-Your pet butterflies.
-Oh, my butterflies?
-Yes.
Want to go see them?
I mean, I want to see the video
that you showed your friends. Gosh.
They're pretty.
What do you like so much about them?
They sometimes crawl up
onto my face like this.
It feels really nice.
It's lovely.
That tickles.
I want to smoke, too.
I don't want to go back inside.
Me neither.
You don't smoke, though.
Do you want to go have drinks?
Drinks?
Are you going to work some more? Then…
No. Let's go.
Just the two of us?
Well…
we can call our friends.
Should I call them?
Why are you laughing?
I don't know.
You make me laugh.
Are you that happy to drink with me?
I am.
I'm sure…
that we feel the same way.
I'm using my wish.
I'm sure he does this to everyone.
I know everything.
Park Jae-eon?
He has no interest at all in dating.
So forget him.
-Hey!
-Are you hurt?
Jae-eon keeps making me feel excited.
Do people have to date?
Why can't two people just be close?
Can't they stand near each other?
Do they have to pretend not to notice
if there's something in their hair?
What do I want from Jae-eon?
You sometimes suddenly act cold to me.
Bit-na and I are going to drink
at my house. Do you want to come?
The two people
the bottle points to have to kiss!
Right. I should just check for myself
and forget about him.
Subtitle translation by: Ju-young Park